漫威出品
捍卫者联盟
第一季  第八集
[季终]
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     捍卫者联草   捍奶联盟
翻译     铁拳章鱼X
校对     捍奶联盟
时间轴     是奶粉袋啊   Avis
后期     拳拳和马律师的8T
总监     捍奶联盟
我不管你说这些人有多危险
I don't care how dangerous you say these people are.
我不想干这种事
I don't want any part of this.
我们是来救丹尼的  但是科琳说得没错
We're here to get Danny, but Colleen's right,
这不是终结
this won't end there.
手和会还是会追杀我们
The Hand will keep coming after us.
现在是我们永远除掉他们的好机会
This is our chance to shut 'em down for good.
他们会一次又一次卷土重来
They will come back. Again and again.
但这能永远终结他们
But these could end them forever.
我知道你和那些人早有渊源
I get that you have a history with these people.
你也是
So do you.
她也是
So does she.
哈莱姆的那个孩子也是
And so did that kid from Harlem.
在这里引爆炸弹也无法弥补他的遭遇
Detonating a bomb here won't fix what happened to him.
好吗  绝对不可能
Okay? Not by a long shot.
没错  但也许能拯救其他有危险的人
No, but it might help everyone else who will be in danger.
你要知道  会有很多人有危险
And make no mistake, people will be in danger.
我...
I...
我就是无法接受这样做
I just can't go along with this.
好吧
Okay.
我先说清楚
For the record,
刚刚两分钟内说的所有话
everything that's been said in the past two minutes...
都太疯狂了
is 100% insane.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是...
But...
我的天
Sweet Sister.
我们都知道手和会的能耐
...we all know what the Hand is capable of.
我们都受到了影响
We've all been affected.
但他们不停地卷土重来
But they keep coming back.
到时候  就不仅仅是简单的犯罪
And when they do, it's not just crime,
那就是恐怖电影
it's horror movie...
大屠杀
murdery shit.
如果我们不这么做  就会越来越失控
If we don't do this, it's gonna get worse.
炸掉大楼  不然就任凭手和会占领纽约
Take down the building or the Hand takes down New York.
这不是我处理问题的方式
This is not how I fix things.
这些人冲着我们的朋友来的
These people have come after our friends.
他们根本没有停手的迹象
They're showing no signs of stopping.
杰西
Jess!
你知道我一开始根本不想卷到这件事里
You know that I've wanted nothing to do with this from the beginning.
那个建筑家的脑浆还在我的公寓里
The architect's brains are still in my apartment.
我都没换过衣服  赶紧把这件事解决了吧
I haven't changed my clothes. Let's just get this shit over with.
一切结束后  我们都能睡个好觉
We'll all sleep easier once they're gone.
我们就能...
We can all just...
继续我们的生活
get on with our lives.
如果我们这么做...
If we do this...
除了那些手和会的禽兽...不能伤害任何人
no one but those... Hand monsters gets hurt.
一个无辜的人都不能伤害  大家能同意吗
Okay? Not one single innocent person. Can we all agree to that?
可以
Yep.
那好吧
Okay, then.
真不敢相信我会这么说  但是...
Can't believe I'm saying this, but...
让我们干点疯狂的事吧
let's go do something crazy.
都是真的
It's true.
你怀疑昆仑的力量
You doubted the power of K'un-Lun?
那些生物曾经漫步在我家园的绿地
These creatures once roamed the green valleys of my home.
这就是它们剩下的化石
These fossils are all that remain.
地球上最后一处藏地
The last known deposit on Earth.
看好入口  铁拳就在某处
Secure the entrance. The Iron Fist is here somewhere.
那不重要了  门开了
It no longer matters. The door is open.
-他必须得死  -当然了
- Well, he needs to die. - Of course.
但是我们最重要的事
But it is in our best interest
是马上转移圣物
to remove the substance with urgency.
其他人呢
Where are the others?
-确保我们的逃跑路线  -为什么要逃
- Securing our escape. - From what?
地狱厨房的恶魔
The Devil of Hell's Kitchen,
不会受伤的男人和大力女
the man who does not break and the unyielding woman.
他们在这里
They are here.
我们尽可能地拖住了他们
We held them back as long as we could.
战争已经胜利了
The war has been won.
有没有胜利由我来决定
I decide when we've won.
等我们转移圣物
Once we've removed the substance...
城市的基石将不停弱化
the foundation of the city will continue to weaken.
纽约城会大片坍陷
A swath of New York will crumble.
很多人会死去
Many will die.
这只是一座城市
It's just a city.
崛起  消亡
They rise. They fall.
你将看到更多这样的过程
You'll see many more.
现在看来  建筑师的计划是
From what we could tell, the architect's plan
将炸药放在大楼的结构中心
was to place explosives in the building's structural center.
这些看上去像是支撑柱
I mean, these look like support beams.
炸掉这些后  大楼就会支撑不住
So without them, the building can't stand.
我们找到后  就安置好炸弹
Once we find these, we plant the C-4.
没有远程引爆器
No remote detonator.
-什么意思  -这是一种定时炸弹
- What's that mean? - It's a time bomb.
你按下"开始"后  就开始倒计时了
Once you hit "Go," You've got a matter of minutes.
-你确定吗  -差不多吧
- Are you sure about that? - Kind of.
-真是令人振奋  -这是基本训练
- Oh, that's encouraging. - It's basic training.
他们教会我们如何躲避炸弹  而不是安置炸弹
They taught us how to run from the bombs, not set 'em.
所以你是说只要有人启动炸弹...
So what you're saying is once someone activates the charge...
就结束了
That's it.
你们俩去安放炸弹
You two put 'em in place.
等我们出洞了  就开始计时  逃走
Once we're out of the hole, hit the charge, get out.
等等  什么  我要和你一起
Wait, what? No, I am going down with you.
上次你们不让我插手  丹尼就被下药掳走了
Last time I stayed behind, Danny got drugged and kidnapped.
事情乱成了这样  你怎么听出说不让你插手了
What part of this shitstorm sounds like staying behind?
这摊乱事是我的人生
This shitstorm is my life.
科琳  他们三个都有特殊的能力
Colleen, the three of them have certain abilities.
-我能战斗  -没错
- I can fight. - Exactly.
作为你的朋友  如果要我去放炸弹
I'm saying, as your friend, if I'm going to do this,
我比他们更需要你的帮助
I need your help a lot more than they do.
-你们保证不会再次辜负他  -我会弥补我的过错
- Promise me that you won't fail him again. - I'll make it right.
是我欠他的
I owe him that much.
这边
This way.
我会回来的  克莱尔  我保证
I'll be back, Claire. I promise.
据我们所知
As far as we can tell,
大楼处于一种高科技封锁状态
the building itself is on some type of hi-tech lockdown.
玻璃墙面防弹之类的
Bulletproof glass, the works.
在每个出口都派设小队  肯定有办法进去
I want teams on every entrance. Gotta be some way in.
什么事
What?
-你开什么玩笑  -怎么了  奈特
- Are you kidding me? - What is it, Knight?
警局的证物处遭袭
Evidence locker at the station was hit.
-什么时候  -大概一小时之前
- When? - About an hour or so ago.
他们刚刚发现  C4炸弹不见了
They just discovered it. The C-4 is missing.
旅馆里缴获的那些吗
The stuff from the motel?
-全部  -是谁干的
- All of it. - Well, who did it?
监控坏了  所以他们也不知道是谁
Surveillance was down, so they don't know who.
我给你三个可能人选
Well, I'll give you three guesses.
-警监  我们还不知道发生了什么  -胡扯
- Captain, we don't know what happened-- - Bullshit.
你只是因为你为他们作担保而生气
You're pissed 'cause you vouched for 'em.
现在的问题是他们打算用来做什么
The question now is what are they gonna do with it?
-该死  -天啊
- Oh, shit! - Jesus Christ.
-赶紧派拆弹部队过来  -收到
- Get bomb squad now! - Copy that.
疏散两街区内的群众  派紧急情况处理部门过来
Evacuate everything in a two-block radius. And get ESU here.
-我们要破门而入  -是  长官
- We got a door to breach. - Yes, sir.
召集完成后我会通知你
I'll let you know when the teams are assembled.
好的  奈特  如果那时候你饭碗还没丢
Okay, Knight. If you still work here by then.
我们要更多增援
We're getting more support!
疏散群众  疏散群众
Get those people out! Get those people out!
天啊
Holy shit.
他们也来追杀我了
They came after me, too.
我还以为杰西卡是在夸大其词
I thought Jessica was exaggerating.
没想到情况这么糟糕
I didn't know it was this bad.
的确如此  已经有一阵子了
Yeah, well, it is. Has been for a while.
我当时  就在那里
Um... I was, uh, there.
他们挟持人质  有人在我眼前死去
They took hostages. Watched someone die.
幸好你没事
I'm glad you're okay.
我们像是没事的样子吗
Are any of us okay?
这应该算是好事
Well, that could be good.
我本来想在电台提出...
At my radio station, I tried to float...
那场地震是在遮掩些什么
that the earthquake was a cover-up for something else.
真的吗
Really?
发生了什么
What happened?
我被叫停了
I was shut down.
谁下的令  你的上司吗
By who? Your boss?
-是的  -该死
- Yeah. - Shit.
如果杰西卡说的是真的
If what Jessica says is true...
这个手什么组织很强大
this Hand organization is powerful.
可能是他们压下了报道
They could've quashed the story.
这可能说明你想的没错  但是...
Yeah, well, it probably means you're right. But...
但是我知道我们能查出真相  我们就是得...
But, I know that we can get to the truth. We just have to...
愿意扑火  对吧
Have to be willing to play close to the fire, right?
杰西卡就是火
Jessica is the fire.
那个家伙呢
What about that guy?
跟你...合作的那个律师
Uh, the... the lawyer you work with?
-马特  -他怎么回事
- Matt. - Yeah, what's his deal?
他是个好朋友
Um... he's a good friend.
只是...他...
It's... He's, um...
很复杂
It's complicated.
杰西卡也是个好朋友
Jessica's a good friend, too.
不是指传统意义上的那种
I mean, not in the traditional sense.
你不能指望她帮忙
You can't rely on her to...
搬沙发或者办派对  但是...
move a couch or plan a party, but...
真的到紧要关头
when it comes to the real stuff...
那种能让你永远铭记的事
the stuff that'll last forever...
女士们
Uh, ladies?
我们刚听到调度令要求所有单位报道
We just heard a dispatcher call for all available units.
-去哪里  -地狱厨房
- To where? - Hell's Kitchen.
一个叫中城圈的地方  44街和11大道
Some place called Midland Circle. 44th and 11th Avenue.
-中城圈  -那是震中
- Midland Circle. - That was the epicenter.
什么的震中
Of what?
一切
Everything.
你说得没错  这地方完全没有人
You're right. This place is completely empty.
大楼地下倒是有很多动作
A lot of activity under the building now.
来  我需要你...
Here, I need you to...
打开这里
open this.
-打开什么  -这是一扇门
- Open what? - It's a door.
-后面有某种机械  -什么叫机械
- Something mechanical behind it. - What do you mean, "Mechanical"?
这有多深
How deep does this go?
很难说
It's hard to tell.
我越想越觉得我们机会不大
The more I think about it, the less I like our odds.
学学我  别去想
Yeah, well, do like me. Don't think about it.
如果一星期前告诉我我要和你们两个一起
If you told me a week ago that I'd be here with you two,
准备炸大楼  战忍者  拯救纽约...
about to blow up some building and fight ninjas to save New York...
是啊
Yeah.
不管怎么说  我很高兴你在这里
For whatever it's worth, I'm glad you're here.
什么
What?
虽然现在情况不怎么样
The circumstances could be better.
但我只是说  很高兴我们找到了彼此
I'm just saying, you know, I'm glad we found each other.
我不会抱你的
I'm not hugging you.
你们准备好了没
You guys ready or what?
-没有  没有
- No. - No.
我听着也是
Sounds about right.
-应该就在前面了  -好
- It should be right up ahead. - Okay.
克莱尔  我要说一下
Claire, for what it's worth,
我知道卢克他们有超能力  但你也有
I know Luke and the other guys have abilities, but so do you.
什么
What?
你救的命  帮的人不比他们少
You have saved just as many lives, helped just as many people.
只不过没上头条而已
You just don't make the headlines.
你说得我都不好意思了
You're going to make me blush.
就是这里了
This is it.
我们怎么判断该找什么
How do we know what we're looking for?
有人来了  有人来了
Somebody's coming. Somebody's coming.
这样不行  这样绝对不行
This is not okay. This shit is not okay.
我会找到你的
I will find you.
不
No.
不用了
No need.
我躲够了
I'm done hiding.
科琳
Colleen...
我们又见面了
we meet again.
我说过  我们命运相交
I told you our fates are aligned.
只是这并不是命运
Except it's not fate.
我来是终结这一切的
I came here to end this.
米丝蒂·奈特警探
是你来找我  还是你跟着别人来的
Did you come for me? Or did you simply follow?
我训练你要相信自己  相信自己的目标
I trained you to believe in yourself and your purpose.
现在还不晚
It's not too late.
克莱尔  到底是怎么回事
Claire, what the hell is going on?
让卢克接电话
Put Luke on the goddamn phone.
打来的太不是时候了
Real bad timing.
听着  你得赶快带着他们逃出来
Listen, you need to get your asses out of there.
你们中有人要炸了大楼
One of your guys brought bombs in the building.
先把周边街区疏散好吗
Just make sure to clear the block, okay?
这里有不少炸药
There's a lot of this stuff in here.
慢着  这事你知道
Wait a minute. You know about this?
克莱尔  不管你们在计划什么
Claire, whatever it is you're planning,
结果要么坐牢  要么没命
it ends in either jail or a cemetery.
拜托了
Please.
你们几个可闯了大祸了  全都是
You guys are in way over your heads. All of you.
相信我  我知道
Believe me, I know.
那是什么动静  怎么回事
What's that sound? What's happening?
克莱尔
Claire!
可恶
Oh, shit.
你在浪费你的能量
You waste your energy.
省着点用吧  因为还有一场大战要打
Save it... for the larger battle to come.
这就是我认为的那个地方吗
Is this place what I think it is?
这些怪物让你我都受益匪浅
These beasts, they've given both of us so much.
不过即便你这样强大的力量
Though even power great as yours pales
与永生比还是相形见绌
in the face of eternal life.
原来你们要找的一直是这个
This is what you've been after the whole time?
正是这种元素造就了你
The very essence of what made you.
而你亵渎了寿老
You desecrate Shou-Lao.
你还打了他的心一拳呢
You punched him in the heart.
昆仑长老们说得对
The Elders of K'un-Lun were right.
他们放逐手和会时太过手软心慈
They showed way too much mercy when they banished the Hand.
所以你认为你要来纠正那个错误吗
And you think you're going to right that wrong?
这就是我走到今天以来的使命
It's what this journey has all been for.
那你就和我第一次见到你时一样幼稚
Then you are as naive as when I first laid eyes on you.
一个孩子  和妈妈一起走路
Just a child... walking with your mother.
过街的时候她让你牵着她的手
She made you hold her hand as you crossed the street.
而你甩开她的手  以为自己不需要她
You pulled away from her as though you didn't need her.
告诉我
Tell me...
为了再握住她的手  你愿意付出多少
what would you give to hold that hand again?
而你还是一个人来了
And here you are, alone.
想去实现什么预言  只为麻痹心中痛楚
Trying to fulfill some prophecy. All to numb your pain.
你休想再扰乱我的心神
You can't get into my head anymore.
告诉我
Now tell me...
你想对纽约城做什么
what are your plans with New York?
气数尽矣  合当陨落
Its time has come...to fall.
电梯
The elevator.
下来了
It's descending.
慢着
Wait!
他或许还有用
He could be useful.
或许你真的找到了你的亲人
Perhaps you have found your family.
大约十层就到底了
Ten stories left. Give or take.
有人在下面候着吗
Anyone waiting for us?
有  大约30个吧
Yeah, about 30 of 'em.
全都有武器
All of 'em armed.
包括两个在车库里和我们打过的
Including two of the ones we fought in the garage.
-那个老太太  -还有那个说日语的
- And the old lady? - And the guy who speaks Japanese.
那你前女友呢
What about your ex-girlfriend?
也在
Yeah.
他们知道我们是来救丹尼的
They knew we'd come for Danny.
两位  这一次
Guys, this is...
要比之前我们面对的严峻得多
a lot worse than what we faced before.
怕你是说轻了
That's an understatement.
那我们怎么应对
So how are we gonna handle it?
我有个想法
I got an idea.
不过你不会喜欢
But you're not gonna like it.
好吧
Okay.
别开枪
Don't shoot.
我并不关心你们在下面搞什么鬼
Look, I don't give a shit what you guys are doing...
鼓捣你们的秘密洞穴什么的
down here in your secret cave thing.
我只是来谈谈
I just came to talk.
事情是你挑起来的
You started this.
自从你闯进我的办公室
Ever since you burst into my office,
我的生活就变成了一场功夫派对
my life has become one big kung fu party.
我不想跟你打
I don't wanna fight you.
不能一个人打
Alone.
走吧  铁爪
Let's go, Ironclad.
我是铁拳
It's Iron Fist.
我知道
I know.
可别累着自己
Do not bother wearing yourself out.
我没有
I'm not.
我知道你的极限
I know your limits.
你能对我造成的任何损害  都是可以撤销的
There's no damage that you can do to me that can't be undone.
尤其铁拳已经
Especially because the Iron fist
给了我们终极赠礼
has already given us the ultimate gift.
无尽的生命
Life without end.
我再给你最后一次机会  与我一起体验
I'll give you one last chance to experience it with me.
成为你应该成为的人
To be who you were meant to be.
我不再需要你了
I don't need you anymore.
混蛋
Asshole!
科琳
Colleen!
我是闯入了什么状况
What the hell did I just walk into?
我经常那么问自己
I ask myself that all the time.
放下  否则我让你倒下
Drop it, or I'm dropping you.
他们要毁灭城市
They're gonna destroy the city.
跟我说点我不知道的
Now tell me something I don't know.
等他们拿到他们想要的  这地方会坍塌
Once they get what they want, this place is gonna crumble.
有我在就别想
Not on my watch.
-亚历山德拉呢  -她死了
- Where's Alexandra? - She's dead.
-你杀了她吗  -不  是她
- Did you kill her? - No. She did.
那个电梯是唯一的出路吗
Is that elevator the only way out of here?
是的
Yep.
我们不能走  我们得了结他们
We can't leave. We have to end them.
-我们有个计划  -嗯  跟炸弹有关
- We got a plan. - Yeah, it involves bombs.
你不介意用炸弹吧
You're cool with bombs, right?
-真的  -想出去就得团结一致
- Seriously? - The only way out of here is together.
丹尼  快点亮它
Danny, light it up.
马上
Now.
-似曾相识吗  -就像以前
- Remember this? - Just like old times.
混蛋  看我毙了你
Asshole, I will put you down.
你让我失望
You disappoint me.
小时候  你一直想有所归属
As a child, all you ever wanted was to belong to something.
所以我才拯救了你  科琳  养大了你
That's why I saved you, Colleen. Raised you.
因为我也曾有这样的渴望
Because that same desire was once in me.
这是你的家人了吗
Is this your family now?
那么
Well...
让我夺走她  来提醒你  你究竟是谁
let me remind you who you really are by taking that away.
科琳
Colleen!
她失血过多  我们会照顾你的  好吗
She's losing too much blood. We're gonna take care of you, okay?
你们得赶紧上去
You guys need to get to the surface.
-我没意见  -你呢
- No complaints here. - What about you?
-我跟你们在上面会和  -什么
- No, I'm gonna meet you up there. - What?
我知道我可以唤醒她
I know I can get through to her.
-你还是放不下这个念头  -我们不能丢下你
- You back on that again? - We're not gonna leave you here.
你保证会带他回去的  别食言
You made a promise to get him back. You better keep your word.
走吧  各位
Come on, guys.
我就来  去吧
I'm right behind you. Go.
快走
Let's go!
你不再躲在你的朋友身后了
Are you done hiding behind your friends?
是你在躲藏  艾丽卡
You're the one who's hiding, Elektra.
你想要什么  马修
What do you want, Matthew?
我失去过你一次
I lost you once.
不会再有第二次了
I won't do it again.
你什么都不知道
You know nothing.
我知道  我爱你
I know... I know I loved you.
-你的心会害死你  -求你  听我说
- Your heart will be your downfall. - Please... listen to me.
-我不想伤害你  -太可惜了
- I don't want to hurt you. - Too bad.
现在还来得及停止打斗
It's not too late to stop fighting.
我们还可以走出去
We can still walk out of here.
一起出去
Together.
就像你之前想要的那样
Just like you wanted to before.
你让我死之前吗
Before you let me die?
不
No.
是他们夺走了你
Before they took you from me.
是他们把你变成了他们的武器
Before they turned you into their weapon.
你不是黑空
You are not the Black Sky.
你是艾丽卡·纳齐丝
You are Elektra Natchios.
你从未做过任何人的奴隶
And you've never been anyone's slave.
多谢你的柔情  马修  但我知道我是谁
I appreciate the sentiment, Matthew, but I know who I am.
手和会没有把我变成这样  我一直是这种人
The Hand did not reduce me to this. This is who I've always been.
你忘了  我能分辨出你的谎言
You forget... I know when you're lying.
你一直想在我心中找到光明
You've always wanted to find light in me.
看看你落得什么下场
Look where it brought you.
你心中是有善
There is goodness in you.
我知道  因为我感觉到了
I know 'cause I felt it.
我不在乎善恶
I don't care about good or bad.
事实上  我从未像此刻这样
Truth is, I've never felt more whole,
完整  鲜活
more alive, than right now.
那我们活吧  我们还能出去
Then let's live. We can still make it out of here.
-怎么回事  -这玩意要掉下去了
- What's happening? - This thing's about to drop.
不可能
No way.
别干瞪眼了  快爬
Stop staring. Start climbing.
快点
Now!
如果你真是这样的人  为什么还不杀我
If this is who you truly are, why haven't you killed me yet?
-你有过机会  -很多机会
- You've had your chance. - I've had many.
如果我真对你毫无意义
If I truly mean nothing to you,
如果你心中真的没有一丝光明
if there's truly no light inside of you,
为什么不赶紧动手
why not just do it?
因为游戏好玩
Because the game is fun.
不  是因为你仍有感觉
No. It's 'cause you still feel.
虽然你说要接受黑暗
For all your talk of embracing the darkness,
我觉得你不想一个人待在那里
I don't think you want to be alone in it.
-我见识过死亡  -你怕它
- I've seen death. - And you're afraid of it.
现在不怕了
Not anymore.
因为你会跟我在一起  在你该在的地方
Because you'll be by my side, where you belong.
科琳
Colleen?
丹尼
Danny!
-怎么回事  -她要失血致死了
- What happened? - She's bleeding out.
博徒启动了引爆器  这栋楼要炸了
Bakuto set off the detonator. This building is about to explode.
-走吧  -等等  我们得回去
- Come on. - Wait. We have to go back.
-为什么  -什么
- Why? - What?
-马特知道  -我们不能丢下他
- Matt knew. - Well, we can't leave him down there.
-上上  -别动
- Go, go, go. - Hold it right there!
大楼里有炸弹  我们得走了
There are bombs in this building! We gotta go!
举起手来  快点
Hands in the air! Now!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能让这种事发生
I can't let this happen.
紧急  紧急  所有警官疏散
10-33. 10-33. All officers evacuate.
疏散  紧急  中城圈
Evacuate. 10-33, Midland Circle.
这就是我们的下场  是吧
This is what we get, isn't it?
居然认为我们能合适
For ever thinking we could make it work.
谁说我们不合适了
Who says we didn't?
我们在一起了
We're together.
这是我第一次见到你时  就想要的
Something I've wanted since I first laid eyes on you.
我们可以永远在一起
We can have it forever.
高
Gao...
怎么回事
What is happening?
结束了
The end.
所有人退后  退后
Everybody get back! Get back!
找掩护  找掩护
Take cover! Take cover!
你得帮帮她
You gotta help her!
我很抱歉  马修
I'm sorry, Matthew...
为我这一路上给你带来的痛苦
for all the pain I've caused you along the way.
我们要死在这里了
You know, we're gonna die here.
不
No.
这就是活的感觉
This is what living feels like.
他根本就没打算活着出来
He had no intention of making it out alive.
马特叫我们走之前说了句话
Matt said something before he told us to leave.
他说  "保护我的城市"
He said, "Protect my city."
天呐
Jesus.
总算能知道
Finally getting some answers
城里神秘的震动和下沉是怎么回事了
to all the mysterious shaking and sinking around the city.
市长办公室确认
The mayor's office confirms
一切皆因中城圈附近的违章建设
that unpermitted construction around Midland Circle is to blame.
奇怪的是  我被告知内爆
Oddly enough, I'm told the implosion
实际上让地面又稳定了下来
actually settled the ground again,
所以我们今天的开始要更稳定了
meaning we're off to a more stable start today.
崔西说
虽然奇怪  但又能说什么呢
It's certainly weird, but what can I say?
这又是纽约市的一天
It's just another day in New York City.
至少  租金还算便宜
At least... the rent is cheap?
接下来  说说你的想法
Your thoughts, next.
《崔西说》感谢收听
Trish Talk. Thanks for listening.
你确定不想让人知道你做了什么
You're sure you don't want anyone to know what you did?
都结束了
It's over.
那才最重要
That's all that matters.
你该觉得骄傲
You should be proud.
想想看你救了多少人
Think of how many lives you saved.
还有死去的人
And the one we lost.
纽约警局没有立案
The NYPD didn't file any report,
所以城市不能起诉
so the city can't file any charges.
据地检官说  都结束了
According to the DA, it's over.
更准确地说  没发生过
Or more accurately, never happened.
那克莱尔呢
Uh, what about Claire?
克莱尔谁啊
Claire who?
霍加斯-班诺维茨-赵事务所为您服务
Hogarth, Benowitz & Chao at your service.
希望你们有任何法律需求都会找到我们
I hope you'll think of us for all your legal needs.
希望我们今后再没有法律需要了
Uh, let's hope we don't have any more legal needs.
尼尔森先生
Mr. Nelson...
我很遗憾
I'm sorry for your loss.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们都很遗憾
It's... all of our losses.
我该走了
I should go.
我送你
I'll walk you out.
那个
Hey there, um...
关于那位有多重生活的共同朋友
about our mutual friend with the multiple lives...
我一直知道那些生活会害死他
I always knew those lives would get him killed.
最终  我还是帮他进入了那栋大楼
And in the end, I actually helped him get to that building.
还是穿着那身紧身衣
In the suit, no less.
如果你在场  就会看到
If you'd have been there, you would have seen...
你做了正确的决定
You made the right call.
我就是觉得我做错了
I can't help but feel like I didn't.
听着  我不像你那么了解他
Look, I didn't know him as well as you did...
但没人能劝阻他
but there was no talking him down.
我认识他的那天  他就已经决定了
He had his mind made up the day I met him.
他爱这座城市
He loved this city...
和这城市里的人
and the people in it...
超过自己
more than he loved himself.
保重
Take care.
继续替他为正义而战
And keep fighting the good fight for him.
你感觉如何
How do you feel?
很好
Great.
不太完整
Not quite whole.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不怪你
It is not your fault.
真的
It's not.
是这份工作
It's the job.
丹尼
Danny...
想说他在这家医院
wanted to say that he has connections...
有关系
at this hospital, and it's a...
是个最先进的地方
It's a state-of-the-art kind of place, so...
"关系"
"Connections"?
医院是他的
He owns it.
他们或许能帮忙
Maybe they can help.
让你恢复起来
Get you back up and running.
或许吧
Maybe.
等着瞧吧
We'll see.
你在喝什么
What are you having?
第四杯
My fourth.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
就是来看看你怎么样
Just came to see how you're holding up.
你不用这么做的
You didn't have to do that.
我知道
I know.
这一周真够呛
It's been a hell of a week.
是啊  我也经历了
Yeah. I had it with you.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
我也该说一样的话
Nothing that I don't need to say myself.
我们之间的事发生后
After what happened between us...
我们都可以换一种方式处理的
we both could've handled it differently.
然而
Instead,
得要发生地震  我们才再找到彼此
the Earth had to shake for us to find each other again.
我对你做的事
What I did to you was...
我知道
I know.
但是  我们得往前看了
But... we have to move forward.
中城圈的事  本可能是另一番样子
What happened at Midland Circle could've gone another way.
可能是我们之中的任何一个
It could've been either one of us...
死在那大洞的底下
lying dead in the bottom of that hole.
我只是来说
I just came to say...
我真的
that I'm really...
我真的很高兴  那人不是你
really glad it wasn't you.
保持联络  杰西
Try stayin' in touch, Jess.
你有朋友
You got friends.
其中一个在哈莱姆
One of 'em is in Harlem.
或许我们改天可以一起喝咖啡
Yeah, maybe we'll grab a coffee sometime or something.
她怎么样了
How is she?
她
She's, uh...
很坚强
strong.
你呢
How are you?
你
You, uh...
你还在想马特·默多克吗
You still thinking about Matt Murdock?
他爱这座城市
He loved this city.
牺牲自己来保护它
Sacrificed himself to protect it.
嗯
Yeah.
我了解你  丹尼
Look, I know you, Danny.
你在找理由为此责怪自己
You are finding some way to beat yourself up about this.
在昆仑  他们
In K'un- Lun, they...
他们教我  每一次悲剧都有教训可吸取
they taught me that there's a lesson in every tragedy.
即便在痛苦之中
And even while experiencing pain...
也有成长  领悟的机会
there's an opportunity to grow and find clarity.
领悟什么了吗
Anything becoming clear?
纽约
New York.
越来越像家了
It's starting to feel like home.
我
I, uh...
觉得我该精进一下遮住弹孔的技艺
figured I should probably get good at covering up bullet holes.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我不反对
I don't hate it.
就好像你又重新开业了
It's almost like you're back in business.
是啊  差不多
Yeah, almost.
假名调查事务所
你还好吗
How you doin'?
还好
Yeah, okay.
-报道怎么样了  -不报道了
- How's the story coming? - Oh, no, it... it's not.
如果我透露中城圈究竟发生了什么
I mean, if I reveal what happened at Midland Circle, then...
只要一个我这样的人  就会发现
all it takes is someone like me figuring out...
超级英雄和律师同时失踪
Superhero and lawyer go missing at the same time.
是啊
Right.
我总有种感觉  这不是真的
I can't shake this feeling, like it's... like it's not real.
或是
Or...
或是就算是真的  也不是结束
Or even if it is, like, it's not over,
因为他们还在挖呢  是吧
because they're still digging, right?
-凯伦  都好几天了  -或许他出来了
- Karen, it's been days. - Maybe he made it out.
或许
Maybe...
或许吧
Maybe.
-跟我坐会儿  -当然
- Sit with me? - Of course.
叫玛姬
Get Maggie.
告诉她他醒了
Tell her he's awake.
我所做的一切
All the things that I'd done...
回忆
Memories...
从不会伤害我
they never hurt me.
但过去
But the past...
并不只是记忆
it's more than memories.
是收买了你灵魂的魔鬼
It's the devil you sold your soul to.
他要来了
He's coming...
来收账
He's coming to collect.